## Ma Ho Ming, Anson

Phone: +852 6198 4541 Email: ansonmhm0621@gmail.com

### **Summary**

Experienced Officer with a demonstrated history of working in the financial services industry especially in banking industry. Highly independent, strong interpersonal and time-management skills with excellent ability of systematical management. Have strong career-ambition and the ability of multitasking effectively, efficiently and timely. Skilled in Operation, Administration, Communication and MS Office.

### **Career Experience**

#### **HSBC**

Sep 2016 to Aug 2017

#### Corporate Action Analyst (Corporate Action), Hong Kong S.A.R.

- Act as a point of contact for clients and financial advisers (custodians) for all Corporate Actions and Floats queries.
- Provide operational and services support for corporate action events processing.
- Handle business partners' inquiries promptly within reasonable time.
- Deliver corporate action events and information to marketing teams for onward delivery to clients within preset timeframes.
- Follow up closely on outstanding cases and discrepancies.
- Complete daily control sheets and report exceptional cases by end of each business day.
- Prepare all instructions within financial advisers' deadline time, funding or system cut
  off time.

### <u>Infocan Computer</u> (Hong Kong) Limited

Mar 2016 to May 2016

#### Administrative Assistant (Administration - Part-time), Hong Kong S.A.R.

- Implement cost reductions.
- Develop reporting procedures.
- Complete operational requirements by scheduling and assigning administrative projects.
- Expedite work results.

#### DBS Bank (China) Limited

Jul 2015 to Aug 2015

#### Officer (Internship), Shenzhen China

- Prepare source data for computer entry by compiling and sorting information.
- Follow up with payment details.

# Ma Ho Ming, Anson

Phone: +852 6198 4541 Email: ansonmhm0621@gmail.com

# **Education & Certification**

Sep 2014 to Jul 2016	Bachelor of Arts (Honors) in Business awarded by The Hong Kong Polytechnic University - SPEED
Sep 2012 to Jul 2014	Associate Degree of Business awarded by The Hong Kong Polytechnic University - HKCC

## **Languages & Skills**

<u>Languages</u>		PC skills		
Cantonese	Native	Microsoft Outlook, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, IBM		
Mandarin	Business Proficient	Lotus Notes		
English	Business Proficient			

## **DATE OF AVAILABILITY**

- 1 week notice

# **Current Salary**

- HKD \$16000